module.exports=
{
    trivia: [
        {
            question: "q1",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "q2",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "q3",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 1
        }
    ],
    ggames: [
        {
            question: "q1",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "q2",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "q3",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 1
        }
    ],
    history: [
        {
            question: "Whose death sparked World War I?",
            answers: ["Kaiser Wilhelm", "Archbishop Ussher", "Queen Victoria", "Archduke Franz Ferdinand"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these nations was neutral in World War I?",
            answers: ["Germany", "Norway", "Italy", "England"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these ships was sunk by a German submarine?",
            answers: ["Arizona", "Lusitania", "Titanic", "Andrea Doria"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "Which weapon was first used at the Battle of the Somme in World War I?",
            answers: ["Submarine", "Tank", "Jet fighter", "Chariot"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "World War I ended in:",
            answers: ["1925", "1918", "1920", "1915"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these people was a spy in World War I?",
            answers: ["James Bond", "Mata Hari", "Benedict Arnold", "Serge Plekhanov"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "How many republics made up the former Soviet Union?",
            answers: ["15", "12", "20", "10"],
            solution: 0
        },
        {
            question: "When was the first Nobel Prize in economics awarded?",
            answers: ["1969", "1949", "1909", "1929"],
            solution: 0
        },
        {
            question: "Which book was written by Niccolò Machiavelli?",
            answers: ["The Once and Future King", "The Prince", "The Good Earth", "War and Peace"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "Of what country was Simón Bolívar president?",
            answers: ["Bolivia", "Peru", "Argentina", "Chile"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "Which Indian president was involved in the struggle for Irish independence?",
            answers: ["V.V. Giri", "Neelam Sanjiva Reddy", "Gulzarilal Nanda", "S. Radhakrishnan"],
            solution: 0
        },
        {
            question: "Who was Karl Marx’s associate and fellow political theoretician?",
            answers: ["Friedrich Nietzsche", "Friedrich II", "Friedrich Engels", "Friedrich Reich"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "Where were the Aegean Bronze Age civilizations located?",
            answers: ["Algeria", "India", "Greece", "Spain"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these battles did not involve Roman soldiers?",
            answers: ["Arretium", "Chalons", "Cannae", "Thermopylae"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "Through which national park does the Continental Divide not pass?",
            answers: ["Yellowstone", "Rocky Mountain", "Glacier", "Yosemite"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "On what peninsula in Washington would you find the Olympic Mountains?",
            answers: ["Seattle Peninsula", "Puget Peninsula", "Washington Peninsula", "Olympic Peninsula"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "Who was the first U.S. president to appear on television?",
            answers: ["Richard Nixon", "Ronald Reagan", "Abraham Lincoln", "Franklin Delano Roosevelt"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "What automobile was named after Henry Ford’s only son?",
            answers: ["Buick", "Oldsmobile", "Isuzu", "Edsel"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "Which state seceded from Virginia in 1863?",
            answers: ["the District of Columbia", "North Carolina", "West Virginia", "Maryland"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "In what American state would you find Denali?",
            answers: ["Alabama", "Arkansas", "Alaska", "Arizona"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "Which modern states does the Natchez Trace join?",
            answers: ["Mississippi and Alabama", "Mississippi and Arkansas", "Mississippi and Louisiana", "Mississippi and Tennessee"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "What is the capital of Illinois?",
            answers: ["Chicago", "Springfield", "Streator", "Urbana"],
            solution: 1
        }
    ],
    sports: [
        {
            question: "q1",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "q2",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "q3",
            answers: ["a1", "a2", "a3", "a4"],
            solution: 1
        }
    ],
    assyriantrivia: [
        {
            question: "Where was the center of the Assyrian Empire?",
            answers: ["Egypt", "Israel", "Northern Mesopotamia", "Southern Mesopotamia"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "What other empire did the Assyrians battle throughout much of ancient history for control of Mesopotamia and the Middle East?",
            answers: ["Akkadians", "Sumerians", "Babylonians", "Persians"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "Who was the first king of the Assyrians to create an empire after the Akkadian Empire fell apart?",
            answers: ["Sargon II", "Shamshi-Adad", "Hammurabi", "Ashurbanipal"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "When the Assyrian Empire was at its peak, what lands did it control?",
            answers: ["All of the Above", "Egypt", "Mesopotamia", "Israel"],
            solution: 0
        },
        {
            question: "Around what year did the last of the Assyrian Empires fall to the Babylonians?",
            answers: ["2100 BC", "1074 BC", "740 BC", "612 BC"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "What were the Assyrians most known for?",
            answers: ["Their fearsome army and warriors", "Their poetry", "Their art and painting", "Their peaceful rule of the lands they conquered"],
            solution: 0
        }, 
        {
            question: "What Assyrian city held a famous library of thousands of clay tablets?",
            answers: ["Babylon", "Nineveh", "Ashur", "Nimrud"],
            solution: 1
        },
        {
            question: "What metal did the Assyrians use to make their weapons, chariots, and tools strong?",
            answers: ["Bronze", "Gold", "Iron", "Steel"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "Who was the last great King of the Assyrians?",
            answers: ["Sargon II", "Shamshi-Adad", "Tiglath-Pileser III", "Ashurbanipal"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "Who was the main god of the Assyrians?",
            answers: ["Ashur", "Nimrud", "Shamash", "Marduk"],
            solution: 0
        },
    ],
    boodaleon: [
        {
            question: "am i ugly",
            answers: ["no", "no", "no", "yes"],
            solution: 3
        },
        {
            question: "why is this category here?",
            answers: ["gun to my head", "leon a gangsta", "forced", "i beat women"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "category3",
            answers: ["cat3a", "cat3b", "cat3c", "cat3d"],
            solution: 2
        },
        {
            question: "category4",
            answers: ["cat4a", "cat4b", "cat4c", "cat4d"],
            solution: 2
        }
    ]
}